# **Nishant Sharma**

**AWS Solution Architect** 



# **About Me**

Dedicated to optimization, and understands the melding of operations and development to quickly deliver code to customers; Has intermediate experience with the Cloud and monitoring processes as well as DevOps development in Windows, Mac, and Linux systems.

# **Experience**

#### Cloudoric R&D Pvt Ltd

Cloud Computing Intern

2021 - Present

- Work with Site Reliability Engineers to obtain DevOps skills.
- · Work with Observability and Monitoring team.

## Ink And Blink

Full Stack Developer

2020 - 2021

- Developed a full stack web product using MERN stack.
- Work with the developer team to maintain and correct the problems in the tech stack and code.

## **Skills**

AWS - IAM, EC2, ELB etc.

• • • • •

Kubernetes - EKS

Docker - ECS

Linux - RHEL, Debian

• • • • •

# **Education**

2016 - 2020
B.TECH - Computer Science
& Engineering
G.J.U.S.T. Hisar

-

## **Contact Info**

#### **Address**

1/36 Naurangabad, Aligarh

### **Email**

sharmanishu.dev@gmail.com

#### Phone

8218006942

#### **Portfolio**

github.com/thecyberbaby

# Language

English

Hindi